[siren wailing]
[警笛声]
[horn blaring]
[喇叭声响起]
All right, we got an EV!
好了，我们买到电动汽车了！
Let's get two attack lines
going now!
让我们摆出两条进攻路线
现在就走！
Looks like the fire hasn't
reached the EV yet, Cap.
看来火势还没有完全蔓延开来。
达到电动汽车目标，Cap。
Yeah, it doesn't need to.
是的，没必要。
The heat's enough
to cook the battery.
天气够热了。
给电池充电。
In about five minutes, we're
looking at a thermal runaway.
大约五分钟后，我们
观察热失控现象。
Should we check the battery
with the thermal imaging
我们需要检查电池吗？
利用热成像技术
-camera first?
-No, first, we make things safe.
先拍相机？
不，首先，我们要确保安全。
All right? I want you
to get me a perimeter.
好吗？我想要你
帮我确定一下周长。
-Cones all around!
-Copy that, Cap!
到处都是锥形路标！
收到，队长！
All right, Diaz,
anyone else in that car?
好的，迪亚兹。
车里还有其他人吗？
-All clear, Cap. Only one.
-Okay.
一切正常，队长。只有一个。
-好的。
-I've got you, buddy.
-Let's get him on some O2.
兄弟，我罩着你。
-我们给他吸点氧气吧。
All right, I got a trapped
victim and a battery cooking.
好吧，我被困住了
受害者和电池正在烹饪。
Ravi, get me
a water curtain on that EV.
拉维，来接我
那辆电动汽车上装了一层水幕。
-Keep it cool.
-Coming up!
保持冷静。
即将到来！
-Buck!
-Right here, Cap!
-巴克！
就在这儿，队长！
[grunts]
Ma'am, steel jaws!
[咕哝声]
女士，钢制颚！
本片由 微博@Tacit0924 网址https://link3.cc/tacit0924 分享
[woman whimpering]
[女子呜咽声]
[woman]
Oh, my God.
[女士]
我的天啊。
Okay. Cap, we got her. Gurney!
好了，队长，我们抓住她了。担架！
Okay, good work, everyone.
好了，大家做得不错。
Once we get our friend
on a gurney,
一旦我们找到了我们的朋友
在担架上，
we're gonna pull back.
我们要撤退了。
All crew set for defense.
所有船员做好防御准备。
I repeat,
all crew set for defense.
我再说一遍，
所有船员做好防御准备。
All set.
一切就绪。
-[engine revving]
-No!
-[引擎轰鸣声]
-不！
No!
不！
[panting]
[喘息声]
[sighs]
[叹气]
-Maddie--
-Don't you look to me
——麦迪——
别看我
for comfort.
You murdered my son!
为了舒适。
你杀害了我的儿子！
[gasps]
[倒吸一口气]
[sighs]
[叹气]
[sighs heavily]
[重重地叹了口气]
[sighs]
[叹气]
You're up early.
你起得真早。
Mm. So are you.
嗯，你也是。
I promised Jee
I'd make her pancakes.
我答应了吉
我会给她做煎饼。
Already done.
已经完成了。
Plus, I made lunch
for both you guys,
另外，我还做了午饭。
为了你们俩，
and a little purée
for Baby Nash.
以及少许果泥
给小纳什。
So you didn't sleep?
所以你没睡？
I did, and I have regrets.
我做了，但我很后悔。
Do you want to talk about them?
你想谈谈这些事吗？
Well, don't really have to call
Sigmund Freud on this one.
其实不用打电话。
西格蒙德·弗洛伊德对此有看法。
I'm having nightmares
about my new probie.
我做噩梦了。
关于我的新菜鸟。
So what was it this time?
Fire or flood?
这次又是什么事？
火灾还是洪水？
Hit and run, with a side
of Athena, but we really should
肇事逃逸，附带
雅典娜，但我们真的应该
-put a pin in that one.
-Okay.
-用别针别住它。
-好的。
Maybe you'll sleep easier
when Harry starts.
或许你会睡得更安稳些。
哈利开始的时候。
I mean, today's
his first day, right?
我的意思是，今天的
这是他第一天上班，对吧？
-[sighs]
-Why do you seem scared?
（叹气）
你为什么看起来很害怕？
I thought you wanted Harry
in the 118.
我以为你想要哈利
在第118页。
Yeah, I did, but now I think
I'm having captain's remorse.
是的，我之前确实这么做了，但现在我觉得
我感到懊悔不已。
Hey, you are gonna keep him
as safe as anyone can.
嘿，你要留着他。
尽可能安全。
If anyone can.
如果有人能做到的话。
["Never Stop (Discotheque)"
by Echo & The Bunnymen playing]
["永不停歇（迪斯科舞厅）"
由 Echo & The Bunnymen 演奏]
[Hen] When you guys said
you wanted to come over
[母鸡] 当你们说
你想过来
for breakfast,
I wasn't expecting anything
早餐时，
我什么也没期待。
-this elaborate.
-Well, you're looking at
-这很复杂。
-嗯，你现在看到的是
Harry's congratulatory breakfast
哈里的祝贺早餐
for his first day at the 118.
这是他来到118号球场的第一天。
-So... where's Harry?
-Exactly.
所以……哈利在哪儿？
-确切地。
[Athena]
I got up early to cook.
【雅典娜】
我早早起床做饭。
[May] And I got up even earlier
to come over to help cook.
[五月] 我起得更早。
过来帮忙做饭。
Except he had already left
before either
但他已经离开了。
之前
of us had even gotten
out of bed.
我们当中甚至有人已经……
起床。
Something about making
a good first impression.
关于制作
良好的第一印象。
I just didn't know
what to do with all the food.
我当时并不知道。
如何处理这些食物？
Well, Harry's loss is my gain.
[laughs]
哈利的损失就是我的收获。
[笑]
Pass me them pancakes.
把那些煎饼递给我。
♪ Measure by measure,
drop by drop ♪
♪ 一寸一寸地，
一滴一滴 ♪
♪ And pound for pound,
we're taking stock... ♪
♪ 就重量而言，
我们正在盘点……♪
-[phone chimes]
-[Athena sighs]
-[电话铃声]
——（雅典娜叹了口气）
-[phone chimes]
-Oh.
-[电话铃声]
-哦。
-[Athena gasps]
-Oh.
（雅典娜倒吸一口凉气）
-哦。
♪ Stop, stop, stop... ♪
♪ 停，停，停…… ♪
Ooh.
哦。
-Oh!
-[laughing]
-哦！
-[笑]
Hey, Cap, you want a mocha?
嘿，船长，要不要来杯摩卡？
Chocolate milk is for children.
And shouldn't you
巧克力牛奶是给孩子喝的。
难道你不应该吗？
be stocking the rigs?
Our new probie's gonna think
正在为钻井平台补充库存吗？
我们新来的菜鸟会想
the 118 is full of slackers.
118路公交车上全是懒汉。
Probie already stocked the rig.
新手已经把装备都备好了。
He's already here?
他已经到了？
-[engine buzzing]
-Aah!
-[引擎嗡嗡声]
啊！
Since 5:00 a.m.
Putting us ex-probies to shame.
自凌晨5点起
让我们这些前菜鸟都相形见绌。
-Right here, Cap.
-No.
——就在这儿，船长。
-不。
-[Harry] Nah, come on.
-[Buck] And by the time
I got in,
-[哈利] 不，别这样。
-[巴克] 到那时
我进去了，
he'd already completed
a mess run
他已经完成了
杂务
and two loads of laundry.
还有两大堆衣服要洗。
Oh, really. And what is this?
哦，真的吗？这是什么？
It's coffee orders.
You want something, Cap?
这是咖啡订单。
船长，你想要什么？
Ravi said you like
that spot down the street.
拉维说你喜欢
街尾的那个地方。
Yes. Yes, I do want something.
是的，我确实想要点什么。
Thank you very much, but, uh,
非常感谢，但是，呃，
Ravi here is gonna
get it for me.
拉维在这里将
帮我拿过来。
Me? Uh, but he's the probie.
我？呃，但他是个新手。
You want him scalding himself
on his first day?
你想让他自取其辱
第一天就发生了？
-Not particularly?
-He trips,
倒也不是特别的？
他绊倒了，
the lid slips, bam.
盖子滑落，砰！
Third-degree burns,
三度烧伤
all courtesy of Buckley's mocha.
这一切都要感谢巴克利摩卡咖啡馆。
No, I'm sending someone
with more experience.
不，我会派人去。
随着经验的积累。
More experience...
getting coffee.
更多经验……
去买咖啡。
Cap, I... I worked
at a coffee shop.
船长，我……我工作过
在咖啡店。
Yeah, coffee is the only
work experience he has.
是的，只有咖啡。
他拥有的工作经验。
Don't worry about it, Harry.
Ravi's got this.
别担心，哈利。
拉维能搞定。
-[alarm ringing]
-Okay. Here we go, rookie.
First call.
-[警报声]
好了，菜鸟，开始吧。
第一个电话。
[Harry] That's what
I'm talking about. Let's go.
[哈利] 就是这样
我说的就是这个。走吧。
Or let's stay.
或者我们留下来吧。
Cap?
帽？
You've had a big morning.
你今天早上很忙。
You know what?
Better that you hang back, okay?
你知道吗？
你最好还是退后一步，好吗？
Uh, what should I do
while you're gone?
呃，我该怎么办？
你不在的时候？
Just take a break or a nap,
you know? Maybe watch some TV.
休息一下或者小睡一会儿吧。
你知道吗？或许可以看看电视。
TV?
电视？
Yeah, it's a long shift.
You know what?
是的，工作时间很长。
你知道吗？
You should pace yourself.
你应该控制好节奏。
-Copy that.
-[fire engine doors closing]
收到。
-[消防车车门关闭]
[siren wailing]
[警笛声]
[horn honking]
[鸣笛声]
[whooshing]
[呼啸声]
[Kelin]
Reid?
[新娘]
里德？
-Bah! [sings triumphant fanfare]
-Reid?
嘭！[奏响凯旋号角]
里德？
Baby, get down.
You'll hurt yourself.
宝贝，下来。
你会伤到自己的。
Mom, I'm SuperReid.
妈妈，我是超级里德。
I never get hurt.
我从没受过伤。
Okay, you'll get injured.
好吧，你会受伤的。
Oh, can I help?
哦，我能帮上什么忙吗？
Careful.
小心。
Sweetie,
you and knives don't mix.
亲爱的，
你和刀具不搭调。
Superman has a force field.
超人拥有力场。
You practically have
a punch card at urgent care.
你实际上已经
急诊中心的打孔卡。
You never let me
do anything fun.
你从来不让我
做任何有趣的事情。
-No wrestling.
-It's sanctioned combat.
禁止摔跤。
这是官方认可的战斗。
-No football.
-Wrestling, plus a ball.
没有足球比赛。
摔跤，外加一个球。
No roller-skating.
禁止滑旱冰。
Who said anything
about roller-skating?
谁说了什么
关于轮滑？
Lance's birthday party.
兰斯的生日派对。
He said you probably
won't let me come.
他说你可能
不让我来。
Baby...
婴儿...
you never said anything
about Lance having a party.
你什么也没说。
关于兰斯举办派对的事。
So I can go?
那我可以走了吗？
Reid, what's
my most important job?
里德，怎么了？
我最重要的工作？
[sighs] To keep me safe.
[叹气] 为了保护我。
But Superman can
keep himself safe.
但超人可以
他要保护好自己。
[Kelin chuckles]
[凯林轻笑]
And someday
you'll be able to do that, too.
总有一天
你也可以做到这一点。
Until then, it's you and me.
在此之前，只有你和我。
Okay?
好的？
Like Batman and Robin.
就像蝙蝠侠和罗宾一样。
I knew you'd say no.
我就知道你会拒绝。
I'm the only kid not going!
我是唯一一个不去的孩子！
You're not other kids.
你们和其他孩子不一样。
They think I'm a freak.
他们觉得我是个怪胎。
It's too dangerous.
太危险了。
-I hate you!
-[pressure cooker whistling]
我恨你！
-[高压锅鸣叫声]
Hate me all you want.
你想恨我都行。
But I am your mother,
但我是你的母亲，
and I will protect you
no matter what.
我会保护你
无论。
[pressure cooker
whistling loudly]
高压锅
大声吹口哨]
[Reid]
Mom?
[里德]
妈妈？
-[whistling]
-[rattling]
-[吹口哨]
-[嘎嘎作响]
[gasps]
[倒吸一口气]
[glass breaking]
【玻璃破碎】
[droning beep]
[嗡嗡声]
[beeping]
[哔哔声]
Mom, I'm okay.
妈妈，我没事。
Mom?
妈妈？
Mom!
妈妈！
Okay, I'm here to help.
What's going on with your mom?
好的，我来帮忙。
你妈妈怎么了？
She's not moving!
Our house is on fire!
她一动不动！
我们家着火了！
1812 Queen Street.
皇后街1812号。
Firefighters are on their way.
I'm Maddie.
消防员正在赶往现场。
我是麦迪。
-What's your name?
-Reid.
-你叫什么名字？
-里德。
Please help us.
There's so much fire.
请帮帮我们。
到处都是火。
-It's shooting out of the wall!
-It sounds like
它从墙里射出来了！
听起来像
a gas line.
You said your mom's not moving?
一条煤气管道。
你说你妈妈不搬家？
I think she hit her head.
我觉得她撞到头了。
She won't move. Mom, please.
她一动不动。妈妈，求求你了。
Mom, you got to get up.
The house is on fire! Mom.
妈妈，你该起床了。
房子着火了！妈妈。
Please. You promised.
求你了，你答应过的。
You and me, like Batman
and Robin, right? [coughs]
你和我，就像蝙蝠侠
还有罗宾，对吧？（咳嗽）
Reid, do you have a path
to the front door?
里德，你有路吗？
到前门去？
-Yeah.
-I need you to go.
-是的。
我需要你离开。
Run outside, wave your arms
跑到外面，挥舞手臂
so firefighters can see you.
这样消防员就能看到你了。
I'm not leaving my mom!
我不会离开妈妈！
Reid, she would want you
to be safe.
里德，她会想要你的
为了安全起见。
I need you
to get out of the house.
我需要你
离开家。
No!
不！
[sighs]
[叹气]
Okay, do you have
a fire extinguisher?
好的，你有吗？
灭火器？
In the cabinet!
在柜子里！
Did you find it?
你找到了吗？
Reid?
里德？
Maddie, there's a knob here
where the stove was.
麦迪，这里有个旋钮。
炉灶所在的位置。
That's the gas shutoff.
那是燃气阀门。
It's on fire.
它着火了。
Then step back. Leave it alone.
然后退后一步，别管它。
But it'll stop the big fire,
right?
但它能阻止这场大火。
正确的？
Reid, do not touch that knob!
It's red hot.
里德，别碰那个旋钮！
天气非常炎热。
Reid?!
里德？！
-[beeping continues]
-Here goes.
（哔哔声持续）
开始了。
No, no, no, don't!
Reid, listen to me.
不，不，不，不要！
里德，听我说。
The firefighters
are almost there.
消防员们
快到了。
Reid, are you there?
里德，你在吗？
[grunts]
[咕哝声]
Reid,
里德，
are you okay?
你还好吗？
It worked!
成功了！
It worked! I feel fine.
成功了！我感觉很好。
Why would you stick your hand
into the fire?
你为什么要伸出手
投入火中？
Do you know
how dangerous that is?
你知道吗
这有多危险？
I guess,
but the house was on fire.
我想，
但是房子着火了。
You're tough as nails, pal.
This must hurt like heck.
你真是个硬汉，伙计。
这肯定疼得要命。
Not really.
并不真地。
-Nothing hurts me.
-[Kelin] Reid's not
your average kid.
没有什么能伤害我。
-[凯林]里德不是
一个普通的孩子。
He has CIP. Congenital--
他患有先天性特发性骨软骨炎（CIP）。
Insensitivity to Pain. Yeah.
对疼痛麻木。是的。
-Wow, that's pretty rare.
-[Kelin] Yeah.
哇，这真是太罕见了。
-[凯林] 是的。
So I've learned.
我学到了。
Protecting him from himself
保护他免受他自己的伤害
is my full-time job.
这是我的全职工作。
He feels no pain,
and it's a pain in the butt.
他感觉不到疼痛。
真是太麻烦了。
-Well, today
it was a superpower.
-[Buck] Okay, Cap.
-嗯，今天
它曾是一个超级大国。
-[巴克] 好的，队长。
Kitchen's overhauled.
厨房已全面翻新。
-You, great work
on that gas line. Good job.
-Thanks.
你，干得好！
煤气管道那边。干得好。
-谢谢。
-You saved your house.
-Not to mention your mom.
你保住了你的房子。
更别提你妈妈了。
All right, let's load up and go.
好了，我们装好行李出发吧。
All right, nice and easy, buddy.
好的，很简单，伙计。
[Reid]
Okay.
[里德]
好的。
-Try and keep this still, okay?
-Okay.
尽量保持静止，好吗？
-好的。
Careful, kiddo.
Don't trip on your cape.
小心点，孩子。
别被你的披风绊倒。
Mom, I'm fine.
妈妈，我没事。
Can't protect 'em
from everything.
保护不了他们
从一切事物中。
[siren wailing]
[警笛声]
[Maddie]
911. What's your emergency?
[麦迪]
911，请问您有什么紧急情况？
[man] I'm at the Church of the
Pentecostal Temple of Prayer!
[男] 我在教堂
五旬节派祷告圣殿！
The devil has entered
Sister Abigail.
魔鬼已入室
阿比盖尔修女。
[screaming]
[尖叫声]
We were exorcising
the demons from her,
我们当时正在驱魔
她身上的恶魔，
and now, the devil's got
his teeth in Brother Isaac!
现在，魔鬼已经得逞了。
他的牙齿在以撒兄弟身上！
When we arrived, the young woman
was on a table...
我们到达时，那位年轻女子
放在桌子上……
...in restraints.
……受到限制。
[groaning]
[呻吟声]
Her blood pressure
and heart rate
她的血压
和心率
were elevated, and her body was
被抬升，她的身体是
-spasming severely.
-[yelling]
剧烈痉挛。
-[喊叫]
[Paul]
But the call
you were responding to
[保罗]
但电话
你当时正在回复
didn't mention any of that?
完全没提过这些吗？
We were told
she had bitten the minister.
我们被告知
她咬了牧师。
But when we got there,
we realized
但当我们到达那里时，
我们意识到
there was something else
going on.
还有其他事。
正在进行中。
[Paul] What would cause
a 17-year-old girl
[保罗] 什么会导致
一名17岁女孩
to bite a grown man?
咬一个成年男人？
It was tetanus.
是破伤风。
-[Abigail groaning]
-Lockjaw. A bacterial
（阿比盖尔呻吟）
锁颌。一种细菌
infection usually caused by
some kind of puncture wound.
感染通常由……引起
某种穿刺伤。
How did Abigail get
such a wound?
阿比盖尔是怎么来的
这样的伤口？
The room she was... staying in.
她住的房间。
There was an old,
metal bed frame.
那里有一个古老的，
金属床架。
The footboard was broken.
床尾板坏了。
[Paul]
What was the likely outcome
[保罗]
可能的结果是什么？
if her tetanus
had remained untreated?
如果她患有破伤风
一直未接受治疗？
Trouble breathing,
pneumonia,
呼吸困难
肺炎，
broken bones from the spasms
痉挛导致骨折
and possibly death.
甚至可能导致死亡。
Thank you, Firefighter Wilson.
谢谢你，威尔逊消防员。
You have 15 years
of experience as a medic.
你还有15年时间
具有医务经验。
Is that correct?
是这样吗？
Yes.
是的。
Is that more or less experience
than you've had as a parent?
这算是经验还是经验？
比你作为父母所拥有的更多？
I parent with my gut.
我凭直觉育儿。
I succeed more than I fail.
我成功的次数比失败的次数多。
Do I keep my son too close
from time to time? Sure.
我是否把儿子管得太紧了？
偶尔？当然。
But do I tie him up to a table?
但我要把他绑在桌子上吗？
Do I lock him in a cell?
我该把他关进牢房吗？
Hell no.
绝对不行。
Aren't you a very angry man,
你真是个愤怒的人啊！
Firefighter Diaz?
消防员迪亚兹？
I used to be.
我以前是。
Weren't you cited
你不是被引用了吗？
for assaulting a man over--
let's see here--
因殴打一名男子——
让我看看——
a parking spot?
停车位？
-That was--
-Emblematic of
the violent temper
那是——
-象征着
暴躁的脾气
you exercised against my clients
while on the scene.
你对我的客户行使了不利权力
到达现场后。
-I was not violent.
-Verbally abusive.
我并不暴力。
-言语辱骂。
Causing undue
emotional distress.
造成不当行为
情绪困扰。
Downright intimidation!
简直是赤裸裸的恐吓！
That's not true.
那不是真的。
That is what colored
any subsequent statements
那就是它的颜色。
任何后续声明
from them to the police.
从他们那里移交给警方。
[gavel bangs]
[法槌敲击声]
[groans] Can we please never
[呻吟] 我们能不能永远别这样
-do that again?
-[Hen] From your lips.
再来一次？
-[母鸡] 从你的嘴唇上。
-[both laughing]
-Hi.
（两人大笑）
-你好。
Abigail.
阿比盖尔。
It's good to see you.
很高兴见到你。
I never got the chance
to say thank you.
我一直没机会。
表示感谢。
I think you had a lot going on.
我觉得你当时肯定有很多事要忙。
And we're just happy
you're back on your feet.
我们只是很高兴。
你已经重新站起来了。
-Yeah.
-[Paul] Firefighter Wilson,
-是的。
-[保罗]消防员威尔逊，
can I borrow you
for a minute?
我可以借你一下吗？
哪怕一分钟？
Take care.
小心。
Thank you.
谢谢。
[Eddie]
Hey, you did
a great job today, Abigail.
[埃迪]
嘿，你做到了。
阿比盖尔，你今天表现出色。
Uh, standing up to them
is incredibly brave.
呃，挺身对抗他们
非常勇敢。
How did you do it?
你是怎么做到的？
Do...
做...
what?
什么？
Learn to be less... angry.
学会少生气。
Time.
时间。
Therapy.
治疗。
More therapy.
更多治疗。
Having friends and family helps.
有朋友和家人在身边会很有帮助。
You know, keeping me on the
right path helped a lot, too.
你知道，让我一直……
走正确的道路也帮了我很大的忙。
Well, at least
I've got the time part.
至少是这样。
时间方面我已经安排好了。
The rest?
其余的部分？
Can't really afford therapy
when I can barely afford gas.
实在负担不起心理治疗。
我连汽油都快付不起了。
Thought you were
in the foster care system.
以为你是
在寄养系统中。
-Don't they have resources?
-I turned 18.
他们难道没有资源吗？
我满18岁了。
Foster care gave me
a birthday card
寄养家庭给了我
一张生日贺卡
and a bus ticket
to my grandmother's.
以及一张公交车票
去我祖母家。
She gave me her car
to get rid of me.
她把她的车给了我。
想摆脱我。
I've been sleeping in it.
我一直睡在里面。
That's the small downside
to being rescued.
这是个小小的缺点。
获救。
There is no one left
to hurt you, sure, but...
已经没有人了。
当然，伤害你是有意的，但是……
...that's because
there's nobody left at all.
那是因为
一个人都没剩下。
Well, there are people
who care about you.
嗯，确实有人
谁关心你。
Where?
在哪里？
[rhythmic beeping]
[有节奏的哔哔声]
-How was it?
-It was, uh, very complex.
-它怎么样？
-这，呃，非常复杂。
Touch and go.
触地即停。
Two kids had their braces
stuck together.
两个孩子戴上了牙套
粘在一起了。
Hey, did Eddie make it back yet?
嘿，埃迪回来了吗？
Uh, yeah, yeah, and he brought
a friend with him.
嗯，是的，是的，他还带来了
和他在一起的一个朋友。
Hey, guys.
嘿，伙计们。
You remember Abigail.
你还记得阿比盖尔吗？
Of course.
当然。
I wish I could say the same.
我也希望如此。
The only thing
I remember from that day is
唯一的事情
我记得那天发生的事是
Eddie's face.
埃迪的脸。
Oh, this is Captain Han,
that's Buck, and that's Ravi.
哦，这位是韩船长。
那是巴克，那是拉维。
I can't tell you
how much I appreciate this.
我不能告诉你
我对此感激不尽。
You've already
saved my life once.
你已经
我曾经救过他的命。
Now I feel like
you're saving it again.
现在我感觉
你又保存了一次。
Well, it's what we do.
Eddie, can I get a word?
这就是我们所做的。
埃迪，我能说句话吗？
I need to talk to you
about that thing.
我需要和你谈谈。
关于那件事。
-Pardon us.
-Sure, Cap.
-对不起。
当然，船长。
Is he in trouble?
他遇到麻烦了吗？
Uh, trouble, no.
呃，没有麻烦。
No, he-he's not.
不，他不是。
I'd hate for him to be.
He's been so kind to me.
我真不希望他那样。
他待我真好。
He saw I didn't have any place
to go, so he brought me here.
他看出我无处可去。
他要走了，所以就带我来了这里。
It's usually Buck
who brings in the strays.
通常是巴克
谁把流浪动物带回来的？
Not that you're a stray.
并不是说你是个流浪汉。
No. That's exactly what I am.
不，我就是这样的人。
My whole life, it was just me
and my mom and my dad,
我一生中只有我一个人。
还有我的爸爸妈妈，
and...
和...
now there's nobody.
现在一个人也没有了。
Hey, there's always somebody,
Abigail.
嘿，总会有人愿意帮忙的。
阿比盖尔。
Family isn't just
the people you're born to.
家庭不仅仅是
你出生时所爱的人。
It's also the people you choose.
你选择的人也很重要。
[sighs] She's got nobody.
[叹气] 她孤身一人。
She needs help.
她需要帮助。
I'm just afraid
the kind of help she needs,
我只是害怕
她需要的那种帮助，
we can't give it to her here.
我们不能在这里给她。
Which is why I brought backup.
所以我才带了备用装备。
[footsteps approaching]
[脚步声靠近]
[Eddie]
Alex.
[埃迪]
亚历克斯。
[Alex]
Firefighter Diaz.
[亚历克斯]
消防员迪亚兹。
Who's that?
那是谁？
That's Alex.
那是亚历克斯。
[Eddie]
Abigail, this is Alex Doyle.
[埃迪]
阿比盖尔，我是亚历克斯·多伊尔。
She's part of LAPD's SMART
program, which stands for
她是洛杉矶警察局SMART项目的一员。
程序，代表
-Systematic...
-Systemwide Mental
Assessment Response Team.
系统性……
全系统心理
评估响应小组。
-Yeah.
-You think I'm mental?
-是的。
你觉得我精神有问题吗？
I think
you've been through a lot.
我认为
你经历了很多。
And part of my job is
to connect people
我的工作内容之一是
连接人们
to the resources they need
to get them back on their feet.
他们需要的资源
帮助他们重新站起来。
I, um... I understand
我，嗯……我明白
that you've been dealing
with some homelessness?
你一直在处理的事情
其中有一些无家可归者？
I've been living
in my grandmother's car.
我一直住在这里
在我祖母的车里。
Alex is going to help you
find a place to stay.
亚历克斯会帮助你的。
找个地方住。
Actually, I... I already did.
其实，我……我已经做了。
You did?
你真的这么做了？
Where?
在哪里？
Faith-based transitional housing
in Pasadena.
信仰型过渡性住房
还有帕萨迪纳。
They have, uh, counseling
and college prep.
他们有，呃，咨询服务
以及大学预科。
You can stay the night,
or longer if you like it.
你可以留宿一晚。
如果你喜欢，也可以更久一些。
What do you say, Abigail?
阿比盖尔，你觉得怎么样？
[scoffs] I don't know.
[嗤笑] 我不知道。
We can stop and-and get you
some toiletries.
我们可以停下来，然后带你去。
一些洗漱用品。
Maybe some fresh socks?
或许该换双新袜子了？
I don't need socks.
我不需要袜子。
Uh, why don't you let the
nice lady buy you some socks?
呃，你为什么不让
那位好心的女士给你买了些袜子？
Okay?
好的？
-Okay.
-好的。
Okay, sir, my name's Maddie.
好的，先生，我叫麦迪。
I'm gonna need
some information.
我需要
一些信息。
I'm Andrew.
My dad's name is Bill.
我是安德鲁。
我爸爸名叫比尔。
Uh, uh, William Schneider.
呃，呃，威廉·施耐德。
He's, uh, 87.
他，呃，87岁了。
Uh, six-four,
white hair, green eyes.
呃，六四，
白发绿眼。
He must have just wandered off.
他一定是走丢了。
Uh, I mean, I don't even think
he knows where he's going.
呃，我的意思是，我甚至都不认为
他知道自己要去哪里。
You think
he might have gotten lost?
您认为
他是不是迷路了？
He must have gotten confused.
他一定是搞混了。
Ah, I should have been
watching him closer.
啊，我本该是
仔细观察他。
What was his last
known location?
他最后是什么？
已知位置？
Uh, his house,
104 Chester Street.
呃，他的房子，
切斯特街104号。
Uh, I'm-I'm here now.
呃，我现在在这里。
All units, starting a Silver
Alert for William Schneider.
所有单位，初始等级为白银级
威廉·施耐德警报。
May be disoriented. Sir, don't
leave your dad's house, okay?
可能神志不清。先生，请不要
离开你爸爸家，好吗？
We have the best people
working to find him.
我们拥有最优秀的人才。
正在努力寻找他。
Andrew Schneider?
安德鲁·施耐德？
You got here fast.
你来得真快。
Please come in.
请进。
Uh, so, still no word
from your father?
呃，所以，还是没有消息。
你父亲的？
No. I worked up a timeline.
不，我制定了一个时间表。
I spoke to him yesterday
at 6:00 p.m. like we always do,
我昨天和他谈过了。
像往常一样，下午6点。
and then, uh, this morning,
I have him on the cameras
然后，呃，今天早上，
我用摄像机拍到了他。
up until, uh, 11:56 a.m.
直到上午 11:56 为止
[Athena]
Oh, you, uh,
【雅典娜】
哦，你，呃，
really keep an eye on him, huh?
真得好好盯着他啊？
Yeah, well, I have to.
是啊，我不得不这么做。
I mean, he refuses
to go into assisted living.
我的意思是，他拒绝了。
入住养老院。
-And he never remembers
to charge his phone.
-Okay.
而且他从不记得。
给他的手机充电。
-好的。
So what was he doing
on the cameras up until 11:56?
所以他当时在做什么？
摄像头拍摄到11:56之前的情况如何？
A.m. Yes. Uh, just
是的。呃，只是
puttering around.
闲逛。
I mean, uh, playing solitaire
on his desktop.
我的意思是，呃，玩纸牌游戏
在他的电脑桌面上。
-I mean, just the usual.
-Hmm.
我的意思是，一切照旧。
-唔。
And then, the-the cameras,
they just cut out.
然后，还有那些摄像机。
他们直接退出了。
I got a notification
when they went down,
我收到一条通知
当他们倒下时，
and so I tried to call him.
于是我试着给他打电话。
He never picked up,
and then I just got in the car.
他始终没有接听电话。
然后我就上了车。
Does he have a cell phone?
他有手机吗？
It's a flip phone.
这是一部翻盖手机。
I mean, apps are just
asking for trouble.
我的意思是，应用程序只是
自找麻烦。
When I got here,
I found his phone on his desk.
我到这里的时候，
我在他的桌子上找到了他的手机。
Dead, of course.
当然，他已经死了。
Oh, uh, and, uh, this.
哦，呃，还有，呃，这个。
Oh, his Life Alert.
哦，他的生命警报器。
Well, do you have any reason
to suspect foul play?
那么，你有什么理由吗？
怀疑存在谋杀行为？
No. I mean,
Dad's a retired math teacher.
不，我的意思是，
我爸爸是位退休的数学老师。
I mean, he doesn't drive,
he barely leaves the house.
我的意思是，他不会开车。
他几乎不出门。
Well, uh, do you mind
if I have a look around?
呃，你介意吗？
我能四处看看吗？
Uh, no. Please.
呃，不，求你了。
[Andrew sighs]
（安德鲁叹了口气）
Uh, he, uh,
he prints everything.
呃，他，呃，
他把所有东西都打印出来。
Emails, articles.
I think, uh,
电子邮件、文章。
我觉得，呃，
having hard copies
helps him remember things.
拥有纸质副本
帮助他记住事情。
Who's Cheryl Sullivan?
谢丽尔·沙利文是谁？
I have no idea.
我不知道。
What is that?
Is that a plane ticket?
那是什么？
那是机票吗？
Receipt. $600.
收据。600美元。
Upgraded to first class.
升舱至头等舱。
No, this doesn't make sense.
不，这说不通。
He doesn't know
who this woman is.
他不知道
这是谁？
Her flight lands in an hour.
她的航班还有一个小时后降落。
He has lost his mind.
他疯了。
[Andrew sighs]
（安德鲁叹了口气）
Here's why
your cameras went out.
原因如下
你的摄像头坏了。
He unplugged it.
他拔掉了电源。
I didn't even know
he knew what a router was.
我甚至都不知道
他知道路由器是什么。
You said
that your father doesn't drive.
你说
你父亲不会开车。
But does he own a car?
但他有车吗？
I took his keys away
months ago.
我拿走了他的钥匙
几个月前。
Where is that car now?
那辆车现在在哪儿？
Oh, thank God. It's still here.
哦，谢天谢地，它还在。
What's usually parked here?
这里通常停的是什么车？
[horns honking]
[喇叭声]
[horn honking]
[鸣笛声]
[siren whoops]
[警笛声]
Sir, pull your vehicle
to the curb.
先生，请把车开走。
到路边去。
[loudly]
Bill? LAPD.
[高声]
账单？洛杉矶警察局。
We've been looking for you.
我们一直在找你。
I'm not deaf.
我不是聋子。
I'm ignoring you.
我不理你。
[engine revs]
[引擎转速]
[tires squeak]
[轮胎吱吱作响]
I assume my boy sent you.
我猜是我儿子派你来的。
Yes, sir.
是的，先生。
My name's Sergeant Grant.
我叫格兰特中士。
Bill,
do you know where you are?
账单，
你知道你身在何处吗？
Mm, about five miles from LAX
as the crow flies.
嗯，距离洛杉矶国际机场大约五英里。
直线距离。
And do you know
what you're driving?
你知道吗？
你开的是什么车？
Yes.
是的。
And I also know that I started
with six quarts of gas.
而且我也知道我开始了
加六夸脱汽油。
So that, unless you continue
to waylay me,
所以，除非你继续
伏击我，
I should have enough to pop by
the florist on Lincoln
我应该带够钱过来一趟。
林肯街上的花店
before I meet my lady friend.
在见到我女朋友之前。
Bill...
账单...
you're a long way from home.
你离家很远。
Yeah, that's the idea.
对，就是这个意思。
Why are you talking to me
like I'm on a milk carton?
你为什么跟我说话？
就像我印在牛奶盒上一样？
Your son-- he implied--
他暗示说：“你的儿子。”
That I've lost my marbles?
我疯了吗？
Well, you can see
that I haven't.
嗯，你可以看到
我没有。
So how about
you just let me pass along?
那么，你觉得呢？
你就让我过去了吗？
Bill, we both know
that thing's not street legal.
比尔，我们俩都知道
那东西不符合上路标准。
But it edges like a dream.
但它却像梦境般美好。
Bill, you may be
in your right mind,
比尔，你可能是
在你神智清醒的时候，
but your son is losing his
worrying about you.
但你儿子正在失去他的
担心你。
You know, he treats me
like a child.
你知道，他待我很好
像个孩子一样。
All he wants
is for his father to be safe.
他想要的一切
是为了他父亲的安全。
Now, I can't force you
to go home,
现在，我不能强迫你
回家，
but I will impound
your lawn mower.
但我会扣押
你的割草机。
Okay.
好的。
-Cuff me.
-Uh...
给我戴上手铐。
呃……
You're not under arrest, Bill.
比尔，你没有被逮捕。
[sighs] But you're still
taking me to prison.
[叹气] 但你仍然
把我送进监狱。
[door closes]
[门关上了]
What were you thinking?
你当时在想什么？
Why would you joyride
to the airport on a lawn mower?
你为什么要兜风？
开着割草机去机场？
You took my car keys.
你拿走了我的车钥匙。
-Because you wrecked the car.
-Some knucklehead
因为你把车撞坏了。
某个笨蛋
banged me with a grocery cart.
他用购物车撞了我。
Sergeant, where does the law
stand on liability there?
警官，法律在哪里？
那边的责任归属如何？
I don't comment on carts.
我不评论购物车。
-[chuckles]
-Thank you
for bringing him home.
（轻笑）
-谢谢
感谢你把他带回家。
Dad and I are gonna
have another talk
我和爸爸要
再谈一次
about assisted living.
关于辅助生活。
I don't need assistance.
I'm a grown man.
我不需要帮助。
我是一个成年男人。
Putting me there is not
gonna stop me from dying, son.
把我放在那里并不
儿子，他会阻止我死去。
People go there to die.
人们去那里是为了等死。
For God's sake,
you were catfished.
看在上帝的份上，
你被骗了。
What the hell
is he talking about?
我勒个去
他指的是什么？
It's a romance scam.
这是爱情骗局。
Uh, people online
pretending to be someone else.
呃，网上的人
假扮成其他人。
[chuckles]
Cheryl is not a scammer.
[轻笑]
Cheryl不是骗子。
Really?
真的吗？
You sent her $600, Dad.
爸爸，你给她寄了600美元。
She deserves to fly first-class.
她值得享受头等舱待遇。
Y-You really think that she flew
across the country for you?
你真的认为她会飞吗​​？
为你奔波于全国各地？
[knocking on door]
[敲门声]
I did.
我做了。
[door opens]
[门开了]
Bill?
账单？
Bill...
账单...
Cheryl.
谢丽尔。
[laughs] Oh.
[笑] 哦。
-[exhales] Oh.
-[laughs] Ooh.
-（呼气）哦。
-[笑] 哦。
You found her.
你找到她了。
-Waiting outside arrivals.
-Yeah.
-在到达大厅外等候。
-是的。
Well, I wasn't expecting
to be picked up in a police car.
嗯，我没想到
由警车接走。
[laughs] Trust me,
it could have been worse.
[笑]相信我，
情况本来可能更糟。
-You're real?
-And even more
你是真人吗？
甚至更多
-lovely in person.
-Oh, such a charmer.
本人很漂亮。
哦，真是个迷人的家伙。
How did you guys meet?
你们是怎么认识的？
-[chuckles]
-[Cheryl] Ah.
（轻笑）
-[谢丽尔] 啊。
The Internet.
You ought to try it sometime.
互联网。
你应该找个时间试试。
Uh, Officers? Thank you so much
呃，警官们？非常感谢。
for everything you've done
to square things away here.
感谢你所做的一切
把这里的事情理顺一下。
And I apologize for my son.
我为我的儿子道歉。
[Athena]
No apology needed.
【雅典娜】
无需道歉。
You have a son
who really cares about you.
你有个儿子
谁真正关心你。
You know that's
all it is, Dad, right?
你知道那是
爸爸，就是这样，对吧？
[Bill]
Well, if you care,
[账单]
如果你关心的话，
tomorrow, get my lawn mower
out of police impound.
明天，把我的割草机拿回来。
从警方扣押车辆中取出。
And unless you want
to be scarred for life,
除非你想
终身留下伤疤，
don't even think about turning
those cameras back on tonight.
想都别想转身
今晚那些摄像头又开始工作了。
-[Cheryl chuckles]
-[Bill chuckles]
（谢丽尔轻笑）
（比尔轻笑）
Well...
出色地...
they got to grow up sometime.
他们总有一天会长大。
Uh...
[laughs softly]
呃……
[轻笑]
Bye, guys.
再见，各位。
-[whispers] See you.
-[Buck] We'll see you soon,
（低语）再见。
-[巴克] 我们很快就会再见，
okay?
好的？
Unless you need anything
before I leave.
除非你需要什么东西
在我离开之前。
Nah. Go home, get some rest.
算了，回家休息吧。
[laughs softly]
[轻笑]
I'm feeling pretty rested,
but thanks.
我感觉休息得很好。
不过还是谢谢。
Poor kid.
可怜的孩子。
Poor kid?
We're scrubbing the rigs
可怜的孩子？
我们正在清洗钻井平台
-and he's sitting on the couch.
-[Buck] Hey.
他正坐在沙发上。
-[巴克] 嘿。
It's not like he's enjoying it.
他好像并不享受这一切。
He looks miserable.
他看起来很沮丧。
[Ravi]
I guess I'd be miserable, too.
[治疗]
我想我也会很痛苦。
Academy superstar
to benchwarmer.
学院巨星
成为板凳队员。
Why do we think Chim's
got him in Bubble Wrap?
为什么我们认为 Chim's
把他用气泡膜包起来了吗？
He's probably just trying
to ease him into the job.
他可能只是在尝试
让他逐步适应这份工作。
Put him on light duty for now.
暂时让他做些轻松的工作。
If he was on any lighter duty,
he'd float away.
如果他被安排执行较轻松的任务，
他会飘走。
Yeah, someone needs
to talk to Chim.
是的，有人需要
和奇姆谈谈。
Good idea.
好主意。
No. No, I am not
doing this again.
不，我不是。
再来一次。
I am not
my brother-in-law's keeper.
我不是
我姐夫的守护者。
Well, somebody needs to be.
总得有人站出来。
I think I know who.
我想我知道是谁了。
[doorbell rings]
[门铃响了]
Ah.
啊。
There she is.
她在那里。
We gotta talk.
我们得谈谈。
I was afraid of that.
我担心的就是这种情况。
Nice bottle.
漂亮的瓶子。
Yeah.
是的。
I read somewhere that it's good
我之前在哪儿看到过，说它不错。
for, uh, flare-ups.
呃，用于应对病情发作。
So?
所以？
Who complained?
谁投诉了？
Who didn't?
谁没经历过呢？
Everyone's concerned.
大家都感到担忧。
What, that I'm too hard
on the kid?
什么？说我太难搞了？
孩子？
That you're following
in footsteps of our old captain.
你正在关注
追随我们老船长的脚步。
Bobby is a tough act to follow.
鲍比的成就难以超越。
Not Bobby.
不是鲍比。
Captain Gerrard.
杰拉德上尉。
What?
什么？
The only thing I got
from Gerrard is mustache envy
我唯一得到的
杰拉德的胡子真让人羡慕
and a PhD
in "scrubbing the crapper."
以及博士学位
在“擦洗马桶”中。
Listen, he also benched you.
听着，他也把你放在替补席上了。
And me.
还有我。
Kept us out of the action
so long
使我们置身事外
这么久
we wondered why we signed up
in the first place.
我们当时很纳闷，我们为什么要报名。
首先。
He had us peeling potatoes
and spit shining the floors.
他让我们削土豆皮。
把地板擦得锃亮。
Harry hasn't even touched a mop.
哈利连拖把都没碰过。
Even worse.
更糟。
How is that even worse?
还有什么比这更糟糕的吗？
Harry signed up for the 118,
哈里报名参加了118，
but you won't let him
be on the team.
但你不会让他这么做的。
加入团队。
Do you know what happened
the first time
你知道发生了什么事吗？
第一次
Gerrard let me
on a structure fire?
杰拉德让我
建筑物火灾？
-But Chim--
-I lost a brother!
但是奇姆——
我失去了一个兄弟！
Last year, we lost a friend!
去年，我们失去了一位朋友！
Hen, every time Harry
looks at me with those probie
亨，每次哈利
用那种新手的眼神看着我
puppy dog eyes, I can't help it.
我忍不住要用小狗般的眼神看着他们。
I just see all the ways
that Bobby's stepson--
我看到了所有的方法
那是鲍比的继子——
Athena's son--
could die on my watch.
雅典娜之子——
可能会在我眼皮底下丧命。
He's not just someone's kid.
他可不是别人的孩子。
Not anymore.
不再。
He's your probie.
他是你的新手。
He's your responsibility, Chim.
奇姆，他是你的责任。
I know that. That's why
I'm trying to protect him.
我知道。所以才这样。
我是在保护他。
But you can't protect him
in Bubble Wrap.
但你保护不了他。
用气泡膜包裹。
He needs experiences
because this job can kill him.
他需要经验
因为这份工作会要了他的命。
He needs a captain
who's gonna show him
他需要一位队长。
谁来给他看？
and teach him how to stay alive.
并教他如何活下去。
What if I can't?
如果我做不到呢？
Then cut him loose.
然后放了他。
Some other firehouse will
be lucky to have him.
其他一些消防站将
能拥有他真是幸运。
He belongs at the 118.
他应该排在第118位。
Then put him in, Coach.
那就让他上场吧，教练。
Who do you sit next to?
你坐在谁旁边？
Whoever is on the bus.
无论车上是谁。
So, there's no assigned seating?
所以，没有指定座位？
Have you ridden a bus?
你坐过公交车吗？
-[knocking on door]
-Easy, pal.
-[敲门声]
别担心，伙计。
Put your phone away
and start eating.
把手机收起来
然后开始吃饭。
Is now a good time to talk?
现在方便谈话吗？
I'm interrupting, aren't I?
我打扰到你了，对吧？
Actually, we were
just sitting down for dinner.
实际上，我们当时
正坐下来吃晚饭。
What are you having?
你想吃什么？
[Eddie]
So, how's the grub
at the transitional house?
[埃迪]
伙食怎么样？
在过渡性住房里？
Alex said they have chickens.
亚历克斯说他们养了鸡。
Mm. Not to eat.
嗯。不吃。
Hmm.
唔。
How old are you?
你今年多大？
Fifteen.
十五。
Hmm. When you said in court
you had a kid,
嗯。你刚才在法庭上说的话。
你生了个孩子，
I assumed he was five or six.
我以为他五六岁。
I mean, you're so young.
我的意思是，你还这么年轻。
-[laughs softly]
-He's not that young.
（轻笑）
他年纪不算小。
[Eddie]
Mm.
[埃迪]
毫米。
I got an early start.
我一大早就出发了。
Did you tell Alex
that you were gonna be here?
你告诉亚历克斯了吗？
你本来要来这里的？
Is that how it works?
真是这样吗？
Do I need to tell her
everywhere I go?
我需要告诉她吗？
无论我去哪里？
[Christopher]
Who's Alex?
[克里斯托弗]
Alex是谁？
[Eddie]
Alex is
[埃迪]
亚历克斯是
helping Abigail.
帮助阿比盖尔。
She's a colleague of mine
at the LAPD.
她是我的一位同事。
在洛杉矶警察局。
Is that all?
就这些吗？
What do you mean?
你是什​​么意思？
I don't know.
She's really pretty.
我不知道。
她真漂亮。
She is?
是吗？
I'm gonna clear these.
[clears throat]
我要把这些清理掉。
[清嗓子]
Oh, no. Do not help. All right?
哦，不。别帮忙。好吗？
My house, my mess.
我的房子，我管它。
Dinner and dishes.
晚餐和餐具。
Christopher's lucky.
克里斯托弗真幸运。
You're, like, a perfect dad.
你简直就是个完美爸爸。
Oh, I'm far from perfect.
哦，我远非完美。
I don't even drive my son
to school anymore.
我甚至都不开车送我儿子。
不用再去上学了。
Uh... Yeah.
嗯……是的。
Chris takes the bus.
克里斯乘公交车。
Says he wants freedom,
but really,
他说他想要自由，
但实际上，
I'm too busy
just working 24-hour shifts
我太忙了。
只是上24小时轮班
to show my face at pickup.
到接送地点露个面。
♪ ♪
My parents got acquitted.
我的父母被判无罪。
[quietly]
What?
[悄悄]
什么？
On all charges.
所有费用。
The D.A. called.
地方检察官打来了电话。
How is that possible?
这怎么可能？
All I know is a ministry van
我只知道那是一辆政府用车。
came and picked them up
from the prison.
过来把他们接走了
从监狱里。
They get to go back
to their old lives.
他们可以回去
回归他们过去的生活。
I get nothing.
我什么也没得到。
I am so sorry, Abigail.
阿比盖尔，我非常抱歉。
[Abigail crying softly]
[阿比盖尔轻轻哭泣]
Uh, it's-it's getting
pretty late,
呃，它——它变得
已经很晚了，
and it's a long drive
back to Pasadena.
而且路途遥远
返回帕萨迪纳。
Maybe...
或许...
Only if I'm not imposing.
前提是我没有打扰到别人。
Uh, I'm sorry, what?
呃，不好意思，你说什么？
-Oh, I...
-[high-pitched ringing]
哦，我……
-[高音铃声]
I thought you were
inviting me to stay the night.
我以为你是
邀请我留宿。
-No.
-On the couch, obviously.
-不。
当然是在沙发上。
I meant, are you okay to drive?
我的意思是，你开车没问题吧？
-[ringing stops]
-Of course.
[铃声停止]
-当然。
U-Uh, yes.
嗯，是的。
I'll leave you alone.
我不会再打扰你了。
I'm so sorry. I'm so dumb.
真对不起，我太笨了。
-But--
-It's fine. Abigail.
-但 -
没关系，阿比盖尔。
You're not dumb.
你并不笨。
And you're not alone, okay?
你并不孤单，好吗？
-Remember that?
-Okay.
还记得吗？
-好的。
[door opens, closes]
[门开了，关上了]
[Chimney]
Harry.
[烟囱]
哈利。
Buck said it was okay as long
as I don't touch the knives.
巴克说只要
因为我不碰刀。
Yeah. A word.
是的。一句话。
Go. I'll finish up here.
你走吧，我来收拾残局。
[Chimney]
Have a seat. [sighs]
[烟囱]
请坐。[叹气]
So, you know I was a probie
in this firehouse, right?
所以，你知道我当时是个新手
就在这个消防站里，对吧？
20 years ago?
20年前？
My first year here,
我在这里的第一年，
that was the worst year
of my career.
那是最糟糕的一年。
我职业生涯中的一部分。
Maybe my life.
或许这就是我的人生。
Look, Cap, I don't know
what I did wrong,
听着，队长，我不知道
我做错了什么？
but if you tell me,
I can fix it.
但如果你告诉我，
我可以修好它。
You haven't done
anything wrong, Harry. In fact,
你还没做
哈利，出什么事了吗？事实上，
you haven't really done much
of anything, which is my fault.
你其实没做什么。
任何事情都是我的错。
You see, when I was a probie,
你看，当我还是个新人的时候，
for a while, all my cap
let me do was clear tables.
一段时间以来，我所有的帽子
我当时的任务就是收拾桌子。
I was like a glorified busboy.
我当时就像个高级服务员。
It was really hard
not to take that personally.
真的很难
不要往心里去。
What I'm saying is...
我的意思是……
...you're not the problem, kid.
I am.
孩子，你不是问题所在。
我是。
You see, I was lucky enough
that there was someone
你看，我很幸运。
有人
here who gave me a chance.
感谢那些给我机会的人。
-What you need is someone--
-[alarm ringing]
你需要的是某个人——
-[警报声]
Damn it.
该死的。
It's okay. You can tell me
when you get back.
没关系，你可以告诉我。
你回来的时候。
What you need is someone
to take a chance on you.
你需要的是某人
愿意给你一个机会。
Come on, Harry.
来吧，哈利。
You sure?
你确定吗？
Get in the rig
before I change my mind.
上钻井平台
趁我还没改变主意。
Let's go, rookie.
走吧，菜鸟。
-Hurry up, probie.
-[laughs]
快点，菜鸟。
（笑）
[siren wailing]
[警笛声]
[Al]
Hey!
嘿！
[Chimney]
That your garbage truck on fire?
[烟囱]
你的垃圾车着火了吗？
Yeah. I tried to empty my load,
but my hydraulics seized.
是的。我试着把肚子里的粪便倒出来。
但是我的液压系统卡住了。
[Chimney]
The garbage is on fire.
How long has this thing
[烟囱]
垃圾着火了。
这东西存在多久了？
-been smoking?
-I think I noticed it
-你抽烟吗？
我想我注意到了。
-like 20 minutes ago.
-20 minutes. Copy that.
大约20分钟前。
20分钟。收到。
Hey, Cap, it's breathing.
嘿，船长，它在呼吸。
When this fire finally gets
some air, it's gonna--
当这场火最终爆发时
一些空气，它会——
-Back draft.
-[Al] We can cut the pits,
-回稿。
-[Al] 我们可以挖坑，
open the tailgate
打开后挡板
and dump all the burning trash
into the street.
把所有燃烧的垃圾都倾倒掉
走到街上。
No, it's been burning too long.
不，它烧的时间太长了。
We introduce oxygen right now,
that trash turns into a bomb.
我们现在引入氧气，
那些垃圾会变成炸弹。
[Ravi]
How about we starve it?
[治疗]
我们不如饿死它？
[Harry]
If we want to lose the truck
[哈利]
如果我们想失去这辆卡车
and the whole block, sure.
当然，整个街区都是如此。
Look, I saw this
in my last week at the academy.
你看，我看到了这个
我在学院的最后一周。
If that fire burns hot enough,
如果那团火烧得足够旺，
it's gonna reach
the diesel tanks,
它将到达
柴油箱，
maybe even the hydraulic lines.
甚至可能是液压管路。
Yeah, or whichever one
comes first.
对，或者随便哪个都行
首先。
And then boom.
然后，砰的一声。
All right,
let's clear everyone out.
好的，
咱们把所有人都清出去。
I want a 100-foot perimeter.
我想要一个100英尺的周长。
Copy that. Cones on the way.
收到。路锥正在运送途中。
All right, fire up a one
and three-quarter inch line
好了，点燃一支枪
和四分之三英寸线
with a piercing nozzle.
带有穿刺喷嘴。
I want an indirect attack
on that trash
我想要一次间接攻击
那堆垃圾
to cool things down in there.
给里面降降温。
-Let's move!
-[Buck] Copy you, Cap.
出发！
-[巴克] 收到，队长。
-On it!
-[Chimney] Hey!
收到！
-[烟囱] 嘿！
Hey, Harry!
嘿，哈利！
-Harry!
-Safety first.
哈利！
安全第一。
Right, Cap?
对吧，船长？
Right. Safety first.
对，安全第一。
[Eddie]
We're ready.
[埃迪]
我们准备好了。
All right, copy that.
好的，收到。
-Yeah, Cap, we're in.
-Ready here.
-好的，队长，我们加入。
-准备好了。
All right, open the red line.
好的，打开红线。
-[metal squeaks]
-[water running]
-[金属吱吱声]
-[流水声]
Buck, how we looking?
巴克，情况怎么样？
Yeah, almost there.
嗯，快到了。
[steam hissing]
[蒸汽嘶嘶作响]
Okay, Cap, we got conversion.
好了，队长，转换成功了。
Let's cut the pin.
Pop the tailgate.
我们把销子剪断。
打开后挡板。
I want a two and a half inch
on that trash.
我想要一个两英寸半的
就在那堆垃圾上。
Harry, get me
those rubbish hooks.
哈利，来接我
那些垃圾钩子。
Harry!
哈利！
Harry?
哈利？
Panikkar, grab me the hooks.
帕尼卡尔，把钩子给我。
You good on this?
你觉得这样可以吗？
-Go!
-We got it, Cap.
-去！
我们明白了，队长。
Harry.
哈利。
-[tires screech]
-Wait. Don't drive!
-[轮胎摩擦声]
等等，别开车！
Harry!
哈利！
Everybody, stop driving!
所有人，停止驾驶！
Harry?
哈利？
Harry!
哈利！
Harry? Damn it.
哈利？该死。
Stop driving!
停止驾驶！
Everybody, stop driving.
所有人，停止驾驶。
[horn honking]
[鸣笛声]
Hey, Cap, you okay?
嘿，船长，你还好吗？
[exhales]
Yeah.
[呼气]
是的。
Yeah.
Buck, Eddie, check the driver.
巴克，埃迪，检查一下司机。
-Okay. Here.
-[grunting]
好的，给你。
-[哼声]
[panting]
[喘息声]
Where were you?
当时你在哪里？
I was at the perimeter.
I was holding those people back.
我当时在外围。
我拖了那些人的后腿。
You sure you're okay, Cap?
你确定你没事吗，船长？
Yeah.
是的。
Possible minor stroke.
Doesn't appear to be injured.
可能轻微中风。
看起来没有受伤。
[exhales]
That makes two of us.
[呼气]
我们俩的想法一样。
Good job, probie.
干得好，菜鸟。
Thanks, Cap.
谢谢，队长。
All right, I need you guys back!
好了，我需要你们回来！
Good job, everyone. All right.
大家做得不错。好的。
-[indistinct chatter]
-[radio chatter]
-[含糊不清的说话声]
-[无线电通话]
[truck beeping]
[卡车鸣笛声]
[engine stops]
[引擎熄火]
Grant. You going somewhere?
格兰特，你要去哪儿？
Yeah, I was just gonna
grab a snack.
是的，我正要
吃点零食。
You think snacking is a good use
of your time, probie?
你认为吃零食是个好主意
菜鸟，你愿意花时间吗？
Go scrub the crapper.
去刷马桶。
Yes, sir.
是的，先生。
And welcome to the 118, kid.
欢迎来到118号，孩子。
Thank you.
谢谢。
[Eddie]
Scrub that crapper!
[埃迪]
把马桶刷干净！
[Buck]
Yeah!
[巴克]
是的！
-[laughter]
-[applause]
-[笑声]
-[掌声]
[Bill]
Hey.
[账单]
嘿。
How's it going over there?
那边情况怎么样？
Uh, last one, and then
I will get out of your hair.
呃，最后一个，然后
我不会再打扰你了。
[Bill]
All right.
[账单]
好的。
-[Cheryl] Mmm.
-[sighs]
-[谢丽尔] 嗯。
（叹气）
[Bill]
Mmm.
[账单]
嗯。
-[Andrew] Ah. Have fun, you two.
-Ah, good.
-[安德鲁] 啊。你们俩玩得开心。
啊，很好。
-Oh, we will. We will.
-[chuckles]
哦，我们会的。我们会的。
（轻笑）
Grr! Dadasaurus Rex
吼！达达龙雷克斯
-is on the loose.
-[babbles]
-逍遥法外。
-[胡言乱语]
[screeching]
[尖叫声]
Oh, no!
哦，不！
[growls]
[低吼声]
Dino-proof. Ah!
How was your day?
防恐龙！啊！
你今天过得怎么样？
Uh, it was good, but I think
yours might have been better.
嗯，还不错，但我认为
你的版本或许更好。
-Hi.
-Well, shift went well,
-你好。
-嗯，今天的班次很顺利。
plus, I got to build a fort
with these two.
而且，我还能建造一座堡垒。
和这两个人。
Who can ask for more than that?
还有什么比这更好的呢？
[growls]
[低吼声]
Let's clean this up
before dinner.
我们来清理一下。
晚餐前。
-[growls]
-[Jee-Yun] Never!
-[低吼]
-[Jee-Yun] 绝不！
So, Harry was all right?
所以，哈利没事吧？
More than all right.
非常好。
You know, the kid is young,
你知道，这孩子还小。
but I think he has
what it takes.
但我认为他有
需要付出什么。
So, no more nightmares?
所以，以后不会再做噩梦了？
Uh-huh. Plus, he saved my life.
嗯哼。而且，他还救了我的命。
Wait, your life
was in danger? Chimney?
等等，你的生活
有危险吗？烟囱？
-Look at you.
You're getting it.
-[whoops]
看看你。
你明白了。
-[哎呀]
You're getting it. Whoa.
你明白了。哇。
Mom, let me go. I got it.
妈，放开我。我自己能行。
It's SuperReid!
是超级里德！
[Harry]
You wouldn't believe
[哈利]
你肯定不会相信
the shine on that thing
when I was done.
那东西闪闪发光
当我完成的时候。
Wow. I mean, I wasn't expecting
your first week as a firefighter
哇。我的意思是，我没想到……
你作为消防员的第一周
-to involve
so many cleaning products.
-[Athena laughs]
涉及
好多清洁用品。
（雅典娜大笑）
Hey.
嘿。
That's the life
of a probie, May.
这就是生活
新手梅。
It's not all glamorous,
but it's all important.
并非一切都光鲜亮丽，
但这一切都很重要。
[Athena]
Personally,
【雅典娜】
亲自，
I appreciate
that I learned three new uses
我感激
我学到了三种新用法
-for white vinegar this morning.
-[laughs] No.
今天早上用的是白醋。
-（笑）不。
You know what? It's all good.
You laugh now,
你知道吗？一切都很好。
你现在笑了，
but just you wait
until I make the interior
但你等着瞧吧
直到我完成内部装修
of that dishwasher shine.
那洗碗机洗过的光泽。
Mm. Not so fast.
嗯，别急。
We have something for you.
我们有一些东西要送给你。
[May]
We wanted to give this to you
[可能]
我们想把这个送给你。
before your first day,
在你入职第一天之前，
but you didn't give us a chance.
但你们根本没给我们机会。
Okay.
好的。
♪ ♪
[Harry exhales]
[哈利呼气]
Bobby's knife.
鲍比的刀。
Mm.
毫米。
[Athena]
We wanted you to have
a little piece
【雅典娜】
我们希望你拥有
一小块
of him to carry with you.
让他随身携带。
[ragged exhale]
[粗重的呼气]
Thank you, guys.
谢谢大家。
I love it.
我喜欢它。
He would've been
so proud of you, Harry.
他本来会是
哈里，我为你感到骄傲。
So, what's in the other box?
I mean,
那么，另一个盒子里装的是什么呢？
我是说，
first one's kind of
a hard act to follow.
第一个有点像
难以超越。
Well, this is what Bobby would
have given you, if he were here.
嗯，这就是鲍比会做的事。
如果他在这里，他会给你什么。
He'd want you to have
your own knife.
他希望你拥有
你自己的刀。
And let you be your own man.
做你自己。
[sniffles]
[抽泣]
I wish he were here.
我希望他在这里。
He is.
他是。
[alarm ringing]
[警报声]
[indistinct chatter]
[含糊不清的交谈声]
[Abigail]
Christopher.
[阿比盖尔]
克里斯托弗。
Abigail?
阿比盖尔？
What are you doing here?
你在这里做什么？
Your dad's busy at work.
你爸爸工作很忙。
He asked me to come get you.
他让我来接你。
Oh, okay.
哦好的。
Okay. My car's
just over there, okay?
好的。我的车是
就在那边，好吗？
♪ ♪
[high-pitched ringing]
[尖锐的铃声]
[exhales]
[呼气]
[engine starts]
[引擎启动]
[engine receding]
[引擎声渐远]